shop everyone ten to five here the very
special vitae and I'm today I'm gonna be
showing you how to make the best peanut
butter and jelly sandwich you have ever
had in your life you will need
grape jelly peanut butter and some good
old white bread because we all know why
is right you're going to need two or
three slices of white bread I for myself
I like to cuz that's in my opinion the
best put it down and now this is
where the fun part we get to block
decorate this now yeah you
missed me well you are gonna want to
spread on that jelly like you are
spreading Bobby smacking socks ass I'm
not making this up actually we'll
start with the peanut butter cuz
as you can see I just took I just opened
it I'm now mmm gonna get some
peanut butter put it on that
bread and I beat Sonic
I beat Sonic makes this for Bobby like
every day and Bobby probably
won't eat it cuz he's like rich in
and it's a copia food but he'll probably
act like he we're cus he wants to make
his happy like you know what I
mean I mean I even made a video
once like what subSonic and his love of
Bobby another song like dunk some balls
and and like the like playing
basketball if Bobby's butt is
sweaty now we're good me to get some
grape jelly now this is a trick to a
perfect emoji house you're going to one
to get some jelly like this and just put
it on
as I said Bobby pie won cuz he's like
he's rich he's got money he's probably
like he's probably buying the great
value company right about now and
that's like smother all and and now
after this you are going to want to just
boom put on like that move it over and
just cut it in half and as you can
see two perfectly sliced be a bob and
jelly sandwich sock slices and but
we're not done yet cuz you know what you
need with the side of peanut butter it
ask called room temperature glass of
milk so I fill that up there like
there's no tomorrow like you ever eaten
in days and how I like to eat them is
just just chow down
mmm oh now I'm all thumbs oh now
trying to get back to focus and
look at that up there mom that's a good
I'll go throw beer no no mmm
oh yeah I want more
give daddy some more that's it mmm he's
out of one you know five out